ALI DEMIR Full Stack Web Developer

Email: alidemirbay2@gmail.com Github: https://github.com/alidemirbay

Phone: 206-832-5615 Linked-In: https://www.linkedin.com/in/ali-demirbay

Portfolio: https://ad-reactportfolio.herokuapp.com/

Professional Summary:

I am a full stack web developer with a background in teaching chemistry. Recently earned a certificate in full stack development from University of Washington. After long experience in education my new passion is web development. I am proactive in learning new skills and knowledge with core competency in full-stack web development. Life-long dedication to learning and in self development. Quick-learner, organized, collaborative communicator. I look forward to bringing my skills and passion for software development to build user focused applications.

Technical Skills:

Browser Based Technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, jQuery, Bootstrap, Handlebars, Local

Storage

Databases: MySQL, Sequelize, MongoDB, Mongoose

Server-Side Technologies: Nodejs, Express, MERN stack, User Authentication

Work Experience:

Sub-Teacher, 2018-2020 Lake Washington School Ditrict Chemistry Teacher, 2000-2018

Taught chemistry, prepared curriculums, organized events in high schools

Education:

Web Developer Certificate-UW-Bootcamp 2020-2021 Master's degree, Dimitrie Cantemir Unv. Chemistry 2016-2018 Bachelor's degree, Marmara Unv. Education-chemistry 1995-2000